Dmitrijs Starcenko

Software Developer [Mobile | Frontend | Backend]



dlstarcenko@gmail.com



Ireland - Dublin



distarcenko



dls-web.github.io

PROFILE

Highly focused software developer with five years experience in a variety of development positions.

Organised, methodical and a keen eye for detail results in solid coding and trustworthy software programmes.

Understanding client requirements and communicating the progress of projects are core values in achieving long lasting relationships

LINGUSTIC SKILLS

English - Fluent Russian - Native

Latvian - Low

CODING / SCRIPTING

JavaScript Python

TypeScript Java

FRONTEND

Angular [2 - 8] HTML

MVC CSSISCSS

MOBILE (Cross Platform)

Appcelerator

BACKEND

.NET Node Spring

DATABASE

MSSQL NoSQL MySQL PostgreSQL



EDUCATION

Ireland, Dublin

2009 - 2013

Ireland, Dundalk

2009

Ireland, Ashbourne



MSc in Cyber Security (Thesis in Progress)

Dundalk Institute of Technology

BSc in Computing in Games Development (1:1)

Leaving Certificate



EXPERIENCE

Software Developer

Jan 2014 - Present

Insights

- **Mobile App Development**
- **Web Development**
- **Backend Bug Fixes**
- **SQL** Scripting
- WiKi Updates
- **Report Generation**
- Support

Mobile Game Developer

Sep 2013 - Nov 2013 **Short Term Contract**

Ninja Kiwi Europe

- **Develop game mechanics**
- C++ Coding

Mobile Game Developer 3D Artist and Animator

Jun 2013 - Aug 2013

Dare to Be Digital 2013

- **Develop 2 player Co-Op Game**
- Create 3D Characters/Models
- **Animate Models**
- Present Game to Public

Software Developer

Jun 2012 - Jul 2012

C.A.S.A.L.A: Summer Internship

- **Java Software Development**
- **Developed 2D/3D Player**



TRAINING

Security Training

Jul 2019

ASP.NET Training

Apr 2019

Penetration Testing

QA

Building Effective Websites Using Microsoft MVC